naijastories.com 2017-12-10

# Privacy Policy | NaijaStories.com

**Cookies**

Our wordpress-based site uses cookies to record session information and store non-identifiable visitor preferences. Session information is encrypted and identifiable only to servers at Naijastories.com. This session information helps recognize you as a repeat visitor and to track traffic patterns on our site. We use this information to make Naijastories more user-friendly.

Naijastories may obtain IP addresses from users either at registration or on individual visits. We will use this information to monitor and prevent fraud, and diagnose problems.

We do not guarantee the security measures in place in our physical facilities to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information that we have collected from you at our site. So, in addition to our efforts, we encourage our users to use unique passwords and to make sure that they are the only users of their sign-in.

**How we use data**

We collect aggregate information on site registrations, what pages our members access or visit, and information you volunteer, such as survey and/or poll information.

The information we collect is used…

to improve the content of our site  
to customize the content of our site for each individual visitor  
to notify users about updates to our site  
When legally required to do so, we will disclose user information at the request of governmental authorities conducting an investigation.

**Deleting your account**

Unfortunately, we cannot currently allow members to delete their own accounts due to the wordpress nature of the site. However, if you wish to remove your account from Naijastories, please let us know through admin@naijastories.com or via the send email page. This deletion will be in line with our [Terms of Use](http://www.naijastories.com/conditions-and-terms-of-use/).

**Email**

When you register on the site or join specific groups, you are automatically subscribed to our feeds. You will receive activity or account related emails from Naijastories.com and the groups. To stop these emails, please adjust the group email settings as well as the global email settings on your profile page. We have made a post with tips on how to do this on the [SITE MATTERS](http://www.naijastories.com/groups/site-matters/forum/topic/tips-to-help-you-use-the-site/#post-3516) forum.

We also send service-related announcements and regular newsletters. If you do not want to receive these emails from us in the future, please let us know at admin@naijastories.com.

**Personal Information**

We will not share any personal details of members including your email. Any personal information or content that you voluntarily disclose in the areas of the site like posts and Forums becomes publicly available and can be used by other users. Please exercise caution before disclosing your personal information anywhere on the internet.

While we’re doing our best to ensure that fraudulent elements are kept away from the site, you may also sometimes receive private messages from such members. Please alert admin immediately if you feel this may be the case.

**Advertising**

We use advertising from Google Adwords/Adsense on the site, and from time to time, we will also partner with relevant businesses that we believe will add value to the site and to our members.

Third-party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user’s prior visits to this website.

Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to users based on their visit to this site and/or other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [advertising opt-out page](http://www.google.co.uk/policies/privacy/ads/).

The Adbrite Network also serves ads on this site based on cookies. You can visit their [privacy policy](http://www.adbrite.com/mb/privacy.php) page to learn more or go directly to the [opt out](http://www.adbrite.com/mb/behavorial_optout.php) page.

Users can opt out of some, but not all, of these cookies in one location at the Network Advertising Initiative opt-out website at www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp.

**Children & Young Adults**

We try to keep content on this site  G-rated but this is not always so. People under 16 are not encouraged to use Naijastories on their own, or without parental consent.

**Effective Date & Notification of Changes**

This policy is effective March 21, 2010. This policy may be revised over time as new features are or as we incorporate suggestions from our customers. We may amend this Privacy Policy at any time by posting a revised version on our web site. The revised version will be effective at the time we post it. In addition, if we propose to change this Privacy Policy in a substantial manner, we will provide you with at least 15 days’ prior notice of such a change by email. After this 15 days notice, you will be considered as having expressly consented to all amendments to the Privacy Policy. If you disagree with the terms of this Privacy Policy, you may close your account at any time.

We can be reached best via e-mail at admin@naijastories.com or through the [contact page](http://www.naijastories.com/contact-us/).

We work hard to protect your privacy and ensure that Naijastories is safe and secure for you to use.
